publish88.com 2012-12-28

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Publish88® is strictly committed to ensure the protection of your privacy online. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform users about the different kinds of information we can obtain when www.publish88.com’s site ("the Site") is visited, the potential use of such information by Publish88® and the options the user has with respect to such use of the information.

We define personal information as a set of data that identify you, such as your name, address, email and phone number, which are private because they are not publicly available.

**1\. Collection of Information**

The Site automatically collects some general information such as the amount and frequency of visitors to the site and its various areas through "Cookies". Publish88® cookies do not collect personal information from visitors to the Site and Publish88® does not complement the information obtained through cookies with other personal information that could indicate identity, user name or email. Publish88® only uses such information for statistical purposes.

When you request a quote or send a comment to Publish88®, we ask for some personal information in order to give you a more personalized service.

When you hire a service or buy product from Publish88® through the Site, we will ask for personal information to register the product or service.

Information requested may include your name, email address, address for sending invoices, credit card number or other information to provide the service or product you require. In addition to the above information, Publish88® may ask for information about your interests so that both the user and Publish88® may benefit from the information online, with the difference that the user may opt not to provide such information.

**2\. Use of Information**

The statistical information collected by the Site helps Publish88® determine the amount of visitors in a particular area of the Site and navigation trends in order to improve its services and ensure that it remains as attractive as possible.

User’s personal information collected with the user’s consent could be utilized by Publish88® to inform its users of other services or products that may be of interest to them. Nevertheless, the user can always choose not to receive information about these services or products, by making it known to Publish88® in the respective registration screen.

**3\. Disclosure of Information**

Publish88® does not sell or rent personal information from visitors or customers.

Publish88® will not use or disclose individual information to third parties with respect to the user’s visit to the Site. Statistical information may be disclosed to third party companies, with which there is a contractual relationship, allowing them to observe how the site is used, in order to provide the best possible navigation experience. Nevertheless, Publish88® will never give out personal information about users without their lawfully given consent.

**4\. Security**

In certain areas Publish88® protects the transmission of your personal information with SSL technology and stored in an encrypted format.

**5\. Changes in Policy Advertising PUBLISH88** ®

Publish88® reserves the right to make changes to its Privacy Policy, in order to adapt to new legal, jurisprudential or technical requirements or for any other reason that may allow for better services and content for their users. Publish88® will publish such modifications through the Site so that its users are always informed.

**6\. Integrity**

These Privacy Policies are an integral part of the Site. Consequently, the use of the Site and of the services provided by the Site, explicitly confirms that you have read, understood and agreed to the terms outlined above. If the user does not agree with such policies and or with its terms of use, you will have the option not to provide any personal information and / or not to use the Site.
